# SWETA VASHI

## IR. FULL STACK DEVELOPER/ FRONT-END DEVELOPER/ SCRUM MASTER

Website - <a href="https://swetavashi.github.io/SwetaPortfolio/">https://swetavashi.github.io/SwetaPortfolio/</a>
Email- <a href="mailto:sweta.y.vashi@gmail.com">sweta.y.vashi@gmail.com</a> | Phone - (+46) 734905328 | LinkedIn- <a href="mailto:linkedin.com/in/sweta-yagnesh-vashi-0062a91a7">linkedin.com/in/sweta-yagnesh-vashi-0062a91a7</a> | GitHub - <a href="https://github.com/SwetaVashi">https://github.com/SwetaVashi</a> |

Address - 1401, Skytteholmsvagen 7C, Solna, Sweden 17144

#### **PROFILE**

An ambitious front-end developer, Scrum master and who would like to join a team of like-minded developers. A good experienced and creative web developer with more than a year work experience in a variety of exciting projects. Technically competent and industry aware means that each project is undertaken with the most up-to-date and relevant programming foundations available. A strong communicator with the ability to convey ideas clearly with an emphasis on client satisfaction.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## January 2021

## October 2020 - Core Faculty and Scrum Master, Codify College AB, Sweden

- Mentored the bootcamp as Core Faculty for MERN Stack for 16 weeks.
- Scrum Master for projects like E-Commerce Website, Project tracker, Portfolio, Weather API, To Do list, expense tracker etc. developed on MERN platform.
- Curriculum Development and Content creation for MERN Stack.
- Monitored technical aspects of the front-end delivery for several projects.
- Write web pages using a combination of markup languages,
   Converted Photoshop layouts to web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

#### June 2008 – March 2020

#### Lecturer IT and Scrum Master, Mumbai University, India

- Software Development Scrum Master for students to create strategies and operations.
- Proposed solutions to improve system efficiencies and reduce the total expenses.
- Requirement Analysis to understand key business needs and documenting as-is business process and workflows.
- Review Project documentation and processes for implementation using Agile/Waterfall/Hybrid methodologies.
- use cases creation from the gathered user requirements and prepared a comprehensive business requirement document.
- Performed user acceptance testing (UAT) to ensure that the product meets the documented requirements and recorded defects.

### August 2007 – April 2008

## Process Associate, HSBC Bank, India

- Enhancement / Automation of Report generation using Excel VBA macros. Optimized data collection procedures and generated reports on a weekly, monthly, and quarterly basis.
- Used advanced Microsoft Excel to create pivot tables and pivot reporting, as well as use VLOOKUP function. Loan files processing, Verification of the data gaps and enrichment. Report generation for default management.

#### **EDUCATION**

Mumbai University, Mumbai, India

2005 - 2007: Masters of Science in Computer Science 2002 - 2005: Bachelors of Science in Computer Science

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- Web Skills: CSS3, HTML5, JavaScript (Vanilla), ES6, Node JS, React JS, MVC, web standards and accessibility, crossbrowser compatibility and Bootstrap 4,5
- Basic skills: PHP, C, C++, Python, SQL, Mongo DB, Agile, UML, JIRA.
- Web Tools: VS Code, FileZilla, Git
- Application Software: MS Office Suite, Microsoft Excel
- Content Management Systems: Basic WordPress.
- Operating Systems: Windows
- Languages: English (Professional), Hindi (Native)
- Subjects Taught: Software Engineering, Software Project Management, Database Management Systems, Python Programing, HTML5, JavaScript, Adv. SQL, Computer Graphics, C, C++, Advance Excel, C#, .Net

#### **AWARDS AND RECOGNITION**

Received thanks awards for cross functional assistance to reporting users for data enrichment & automation at HSBC Mumbai, India. (2007 & 08).

#### **REFERENCES**

1) Anurag Garg, Swed Bank, Sweden

Phone: +46 734769931

2) Bindu Trikha, Codify College AB, Sweden

Phone: +47 40969175